Outlands police representatives join the
hunt after the disappearance of the
Carlisle expedition no word of the party
has been received in nearly two months
Carlisle and his party who reportedly
intended to explore portions of the
Great Rift Valley Northwest of Nairobi
the expedition left Nairobi on August
the 3rd ostensibly on a camera Safari
but rumal assisted they were actually
seeking legendary biblical treasures in
the response to clues Miss Erica
Carlisle sister to the American leader
of the lost Carlisle expedition arrived
in Port aboard the Egyptian vessel font
of life
miss Carlisle declared her intentions to
find her brother regardless of the
effort needed she brought with her the
nucleus of a large expedition tragically
the massacre of the long missing
Carlisle expedition was later confirmed
by district police representatives Roger
Carlisle New York's rollicking pay boy
is counted amongst the missing
Erica Carlisle Roger Carlisle sister and
apart heiress to the Carlyle family
fortune led the dangerous search for her
brother and his party she credited
Kikuyu tribesmen for the discovery
amongst other expedition members
believed lost are sir or bleep NQ noted
Egyptologist New York socialite Hypatia
masters and dr. Robert Weston many
bearers are also reported to be dead
five Nandi tribesmen convicted
ringleaders of the vicious Carlile
expedition massacre were executed soon
after following a short expertly
conducted trial the end the tribesman
steadfastly refused to reveal where they
had hidden the bodies of the white
leaders of the expedition it is thought
that the first being victims were taken
to a secret location there to suffer the
most savage treatment Miss Erica
Carlisle despite defeats in their
efforts to rescue her brother is surely
now comforted by the triumph of justice