roger carlisle the playboy who
everyone knows or knows about is quietly
leaving new york tomorrow to check out
the tombs of egypt
you've seen the cuties roger has found
in the night spots who can doubt he'll
dig up someone i'm
something equally fabulous from the
egyptian sands
led by the fabulously wealthy play by
roger carlisle the carlisle expedition
departed this morning for southampton
aboard the crack british steamship
imperial standard contrary to earlier
reports
the expedition will perform researches
in london under the auspices of the
penhue foundation
before continuing to egypt next month
scandal and indelicate behavior have
become carlisle's trademark but he has
never become tarnished in the eyes of
manhattanites
renowned egyptologist so aubrey penhu is
the assistant team leader
dr robert huston a fashionable freudian
psychologist
accompanies the expedition to pursue
parallel researches
miss hypatia masters linked in the past
to carlisle will act as photographer
and archivist
alas it seems that the heat has got the
better of our great white adventurers
as after a short time in egypt so aubry
penhue
the temporary spokesman for the carlisle
expedition has indicated that the
leaders are taking ship to east africa
for a well-earned rest
sorobli debunked rumors that the
expedition had discovered clues to the
legendary wealth of the lost minds of
king solomon
maintaining that the party was simply
going on safari
roger carlisle wealthy new york leader
of the expedition was unavailable for
comment
still suffering from his recent
sunstroke
you